Sheet Music Collection
Sheet Music Collection
- Opera items
  - Scores
    - Bemberg, Henri The Death of Joan of Arc: an historic scene –arranged by Max Spicker, taken from "Les Messéniennes," by Casimir Delavigne, English version by Henry G. Chapman (Box 10)
    - Clough-Leighter, H. Cantatas for Women's Voices: Across the Fields to Anne! – (Op. 30), lyric by Richard Burton, (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Box 10)
    - Gaul, Harvey B. The Babe of Bethlehem: a Christmas Cantata, two copies, one signed by Mrs. Cora Girten (Box 10)
    - Holton, Fred B. Lorenz's Choir Cantatas: The Christmas King (Box 10)
    - Maunder, J. H. Olivet to Calvary – words by Shapcott Wensley (Box 10)
    - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, F. G. Schirmer's Collection of Oratorios and Cantatas: The First Walpurgis Night (Op. 60), English version by W. Bartholemew, two copies, one signed "Winifred Seely Myers" (Box 10)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix Elijah: an Oratorio, (signed "Winifred S. Myers 29") (Box 10)
    - Petrie, H. W. The Greatest Gift: Christmas Cantata – words by R. Bronner (Box 10)
    - Read, Angelo M. David's Lament: a Song of Love – (Op. 15) (Box 10)
    - Sullivan, Arthur Iolanthe, or, The Peer and the Peri – written by W. S. Gilbert, two copies (Box 10)
    - Sullivan, Arthur Patience, or, Bunthorne's Bride – written by W. S. Gilbert (Box 10)
    - Sullivan, Arthur The Sorcerer: an Original Modern Comic Opera – written by W. S. Gilbert, two copies (Box 10)
    - Sullivan, Arthur Trial By Jury: a Novel and Original Dramatic Cantata – words by W. S. Gilbert (Box 10)
- Owner-bound sheet music
  - [Volume 1], sheet music bound post-publication. Owner attributions include Mary H. Brown, Genie E. V. Camp, A. Egan, M. L. A. Egan, Mary H. B. Hitt, and Fannie A. Nye (Box 11)
  - [Volume 2], sheet music bound post-publication. Owner attributions include Emily Osborne, T. M. Osborne, Olmstead, Nettie W. Ryon, and W. Pelham Wright. (Box 12)
  - [Volume 3], sheet music bound post-publication. Owners are not attributed (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous
  - Church bulletins
    - Various, includes Boardwalk Church at New York Avenue in Atlantic City, N. J. and the First M. E. and Presbyterian Churches in Berwick, Pa (Oversize 14)
  - Catalogues
    - Various, catalogues from Leiter Bros. of Syracuse, NY, Ramos & Moses of Richmond, Va., and Henry C. Wyatt of Richmond, Va (Oversize 14)
  - Periodicals
    - Clippings, clippings from The Etude, The School Century, Woman's Home Companion, The New York Times (Oversize 14)
    - Complete, full copies of or supplements to Harper's Young People, Lauter Co.'s Musical Journal, The New York Sunday Press, and North's Philadelphia Musical Journal (Oversize 14)
  - Fragments
    - Covers, covers (front and back when available) detached from their respective pieces of sheet music or books (Oversize 15)
    - Sheet music, fragments of sheet music other than simply the covers. Incomplete copies of pieces are also included. (Oversize 15)
    - Collections of music, books, fragments from books or collections of music (usually determined by size or page number[s]); 2 folders (Oversize 15)
    - Other, fragments of indeterminate origin or which seem to not be from periodicals, sheet music, collections of music, or books (Oversize 15)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Various, programs from non-opera performances, manuscripts of music, poems, and other unique items (Oversize 14)